rxconsultant.com 2014-02-18

# Privacy Policy - The Rx Consultant

We invite you to ask us about any privacy concern you may have by calling 1-800-798-3353. 

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) 
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * To process transactions  

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the product purchased or service requested. 

  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails  

> The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional news from The Rx Consultant, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, etc.) will not be stored on our servers. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enable the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

### Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

_This policy was last modified on 1/21/2010_

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

**Continuing Education Network, Inc.**  
P.O. Box 1516  
Martinez, California 94553  
**Email:** [rxmail@rxconsultant.com](mailto:rxmail@rxconsultant.com)  
**Phone:** 1-800-798-3353  
**Site:** [www.rxconsultant.com](http://www.rxconsultant.com/)
